Welcome back to this court, so honest for you that, first of all, our nation in this first video
of the session supported, I will use a political presentation, which is quite popular package for
the nation.
And this president looks like this here.
OK, so first of all, it's all this president from here go back and I simply go to the new terminal
and put that here and install it.
And then I go to my components and the home component.
First of all, import that, so import the veggie nation from the.
Oops, Vasteras dash pagination, and then I will use it after this section for displaying all the product
rooms.
So pagination.
And we have to actually wrap it inside.
A empty bags.
Like this and the pictures, we have to pass a lot of options, actually, first of all, I have to
display the active page.
So what is the active page of the portrait?
Later than I have also posted here the items on the page.
OK, so how many items want to display per page?
So for that I have to actually import from here.
On the state results page, then I will stay here, the room's count and then the filtered count like
this, so I will simply pass deserves a page right here, then have to pass.
The total items count so total items count in the rooms, count how many items have that is rooms count
all you have to give up on change.
That is basically a function.
So then the debate is change.
I have to do something, some sort of I set.
Front page.
No, I have the past couple of options, first of all, of the next page is equal to for next page text.
OK, that is going to be next.
These rules are not required.
This one is not required.
But I want to display the next and previous.
Also, OK, so for the previous display here, the previous model, if I go there, you can see that
here by default it will display these icons.
So I want to replace that for the next page, I believe.
What's next for the previous type here?
Previous and these are.
And this button and this is the first page and the last page.
So I'll use coastland last after next to previous.
I also have right here first page text.
That is going to be first.
Then we have the last page text which is last, then display here, pass here the item
Glaus.
That is the item, because I have override these glasses.
I have changed the color and the UI a little bit, you can find those in the scenes.
That's fine, actually, if I go to Styles and global access.
And I called the these.
Some of them here, you will see that I have changed from color to the page color, paging over color.
So you have this over these tiles not as defined as function alerts, actually call this handle pagination
like this.
OK, simply copied from here.
Goldthorpe and I defined out here so const handle pagination.
That is going to a function that will have the page number, which is the current page number that should
not give us, and then after getting the page and I simply have to go to that particular page number
of that products, what I do is right here, window door location, thought he should have is going
to be able to slash, which is the home page.
But now I will pass here.
That is called Page.
What is the page that pages page number that this will give us pagination.
OK, first of it.
And what is the error?
But we have to give the activation number, so now we are setting the page in the query so you can get
the biscuit from the query, a similar type here calls the page from Roder query.
And we also have to import the water from the next selection order.
So import use, rather, from next.
Slash Roger and then I have to use this.
OK, it's not from the doctor or the current number, which is which will be in here.
OK, so by default there is not any page numbers also written here that by default the patient is going
to be one like this and.
And from the work we do, we get back our page in form of string, so we have to read that a number.
The the the page is equal to number and parts of the page, and we are overriding the value of page
led by default.
If you go to the home page without any page query, then in that case the patient is going to be one
by default and it can give us in springform.
So we convert that into the number.
And now I will pass this page as the current page in our active page like this subliterate and also
go back.
Let's close this one a little page.
You will see that you to have a patient here, surgical center as we go about maybe a score.
And what I do is I first of all, to type here a check that if reserves are paid is less, then so if
reserves per page is less, then the rules count.
OK, then I have to pay attention.
All right.
So I simply
this.
OK.
So, for example, if the rumors are true and that's what we are just for, for definitely it doesn't
make any sense to discredit pagination.
So make sure that the results are paid is less than the rumors count.
OK, in this case only seven and eight is false or distraught to sample it.
I give it a glass display, Fleck's moocher class and then I type here justify.
Content center to center, and then I will also moderate both sides like this, and then I got this
live and wrapped inside that is like this and now I go back.
Now it is centered so I can see that we are getting only here two pages, one and two, because Fusspot
products are on first page and millions of products are on my second page.
If I want to, you will see that it goes to this is all pages equal to page number two.
But the products are the same because we also have to participate on our backend.
So now we successfully get paid is equal to what I do is I simply go back on your score and in the pages
in or whether it is index in those index number, you also have access here of quitte.
OK.
We as we have access to the programs, we also have access to liquidity, so nobody can pass here after
request.
I can also pass here the equity page.
OK, but what is the current page number?
Simply save it and then go back to my actions.
So the actions, actions and now here I will get my request and also have a look at the current page
number.
So by default, that is also going to be one here.
OK, if we don't get back any to page, no defaults on the first page.
So after the runes, I simply have to pass in here that page.
Is equal to the current rate like this and are also sending the request the back and if to go back.
Reload page, you will see that now on page two and we are seeing the military are rooms, if I go to
one more page called one and we are displaying all the rooms.
And even though if I remove this page and now is on the one to go to, if I go back to my escort in
the controllers room controllers, I change per page proposal.
It.
So close, this one, this one month ago, back if I paid, you will see that on page two.
We have one group products, but now we have these four pages here because now they are displaying truisms
but bit like this.
OK, so this one that was also implemented successfully here, I hope I understand in my next video,
I will also handle this search functionality in this project.
OK, so I will see you the next video.